<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NovenApp</string>
    <string name="novena_aguinaldos_title">Novena of Aguinaldos</string>
    <string name="text_ir_al_principio">Go to the beginning</string>
    <string name="text_siguiente">Next</string>
    <string name="text_anterior">Previous</string>
    <string name="text_ir_a">Go to day %s</string>
    <string name="text_regresa">Back</string>
    <string name="text_ir_a_inicio">Home</string>
    <string name="text_consideration">Consideration for day %d</string>
    <string name="text_dia">Day %d</string>
    <string name="text_tiempo_llegado">The time has come!</string>
    <string name="text_navidad_en">Christmas in:</string>
    <string name="text_navidad_en_yy_mm_dd">"%d days, %d hours, %d minutes, %d seconds"</string>
    <string name="gozos_title">Gozos</string>
    <string name="our_father_title">Our Father</string>
    <string name="hail_mary_title">Hail Mary</string>
    <string name="glory_be_title">Glory Be</string>
    <string name="divine_child_title">Divine Child</string>
    <string name="text_music">Music</string>
    <string name="text_novena_days">"Novena days"</string>
    <string name="text_villancicos">Christmas carol"</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="text_lyrics">Sing Along with Lyrics</string>
    <string name="oracion_todos_los_dias">Prayer for Every Day</string>
    <string name="oracion_a_la_virgen">Prayer to the Virgin</string>
    <string name="oracion_a_san_jose">Prayer to Saint Joseph</string>
    <string name="consideracion">Reflection</string>
    <string name="oracion_a_jesus">Prayer to the Child Jesus</string>
    <string name="gozos">Jubilant Verses</string>
    <string name="text_help_and_fb">Help and feedback</string>
    <string name="text_about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="text_rate_this_app">Rate this app</string>
    <string name="text_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="text_follow_us">Follow us on social networks</string>


    <string name="about_us_outrageous_cat_section_title">Outrageous Cat</string>
    <string name="about_us_outrageous_cat_slogan"> The art of simplicity to solve problems intelligently, practically, and efficiently. Say goodbye to complications!</string>
    <string name="about_us_outrageous_cat_philosophy_text">We believe simplicity is the most elegant way to solve problems. Our goal is to turn everyday challenges into agile, easy-to-use solutions (because who needs unnecessary manuals?).\n\nWe were born with the idea of simplifying the complex through smart apps. Since then, we\'ve focused on creating functional tools that are as intuitive as they are practical.\n\nYour feedback drives us. We\'re always striving to improve, offering experiences that make your life simpler and more enjoyable.</string>
    <string name="about_us_shuffle_friends_slogan">Drawing a Secret Santa should be simple. With Shuffle Friends, it is. Have fun, choose, and enjoy without the hassle.</string>
    <string name="about_us_shuffle_friends_description_text">NovenApp is the perfect companion for celebrating the traditional Novena de Aguinaldos in Colombia. Designed to bring families and friends together during the Christmas season, our app offers a beautifully crafted experience with prayers, villancicos, and interactive features that enhance this cherished tradition.
            \nWith NovenApp, you can follow each day\'s novena with ease, sing along to classic villancicos to add rhythm to your celebrations.
            \nOur mission is to keep this beautiful tradition alive in the digital age, making it more accessible and engaging for everyone. Whether at home, with friends, or on the go, NovenApp helps you connect with the Christmas spirit in a meaningful way.
            \n¡Join us in celebrating this special time of year with NovenApp! 🎄✨</string>
    <string name="about_us_shuffle_friends_app_info_label">App information:</string>

    <string name="our_father">
    Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name; thy kingdom come; thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
    Give us this day our daily bread; and forgive us our trespasses, as we forgive those who trespass against us;
    and lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil. Amen.
    </string>

    <string name="hail_mary">
    Hail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee. Blessed art thou among women,
    and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus. Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
    now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
    </string>

    <string name="glory_be">
    Glory be to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit.
    As it was in the beginning, is now, and ever shall be, world without end. Amen.
    </string>

    <string name="divine_child">
    - Oh Divine Child Jesus
    - (All) Bless us with love
    </string>


</resources>